I wanted to make this video to show you
I wanted to make this video to show you how to actually make money with AI. Last
how to actually make money with AI. Last
how to actually make money with AI. Last month, my AI agency, Gym Members Now,
month, my AI agency, Gym Members Now,
month, my AI agency, Gym Members Now, was valued at
was valued at
was valued at $5,448,000, and it has generated
$5,448,000, and it has generated
$5,448,000, and it has generated 5,736,31 in profit from 2021 up until
5,736,31 in profit from 2021 up until
5,736,31 in profit from 2021 up until 2024, and we're still cranking. But my
2024, and we're still cranking. But my
2024, and we're still cranking. But my agency is now worth over $5 million
agency is now worth over $5 million
agency is now worth over $5 million through selling AI agents or basic
through selling AI agents or basic
through selling AI agents or basic automated flows is through leveraging a
automated flows is through leveraging a
automated flows is through leveraging a new system of AI services that work
new system of AI services that work
new system of AI services that work complimentary to each other. And by
complimentary to each other. And by
complimentary to each other. And by doing it this way, I generate my clients
doing it this way, I generate my clients
doing it this way, I generate my clients atypical results. I charge more. I
atypical results. I charge more. I
atypical results. I charge more. I retain them a lot longer and I close at
retain them a lot longer and I close at
retain them a lot longer and I close at a much higher rate because there's no
a much higher rate because there's no
a much higher rate because there's no one else in the marketplace offering it
one else in the marketplace offering it
one else in the marketplace offering it in the sequential order that I offer it
in the sequential order that I offer it
in the sequential order that I offer it in. And in this video, I'm pulling back
in. And in this video, I'm pulling back
in. And in this video, I'm pulling back the curtain. I'm going to show you the
the curtain. I'm going to show you the
the curtain. I'm going to show you the exact system, live examples of it with
exact system, live examples of it with
exact system, live examples of it with clients active right now, leveraging
clients active right now, leveraging
clients active right now, leveraging this exact system. And then I'm also
this exact system. And then I'm also
this exact system. And then I'm also going to show you how to sell this exact
going to show you how to sell this exact
going to show you how to sell this exact same AI system and break it down so that
same AI system and break it down so that
same AI system and break it down so that you can just copy me. Let me tell you
you can just copy me. Let me tell you
you can just copy me. Let me tell you why I'm doing this, though. So, my
why I'm doing this, though. So, my
why I'm doing this, though. So, my agency is worth $5.4 million. If I can
agency is worth $5.4 million. If I can
agency is worth $5.4 million. If I can help three to four other people do what
help three to four other people do what
help three to four other people do what I've done in the same market or even in
I've done in the same market or even in
I've done in the same market or even in different markets, we can roll our
different markets, we can roll our
different markets, we can roll our companies up into a portfolio and sell
companies up into a portfolio and sell
companies up into a portfolio and sell for two to three times more than what we
for two to three times more than what we
for two to three times more than what we would get independently selling. So
would get independently selling. So
would get independently selling. So there's a huge opportunity for both of
there's a huge opportunity for both of
there's a huge opportunity for both of us if that's what you're trying to do.
us if that's what you're trying to do.
us if that's what you're trying to do. So let's jump into it. So right here,
So let's jump into it. So right here,
So let's jump into it. So right here, what you're looking at is the valuation
what you're looking at is the valuation
what you're looking at is the valuation that I had done by Value Buddy. It's a
that I had done by Value Buddy. It's a
that I had done by Value Buddy. It's a company that valuates companies. You can
company that valuates companies. You can
company that valuates companies. You can look them up. They're very legit. I paid
look them up. They're very legit. I paid
look them up. They're very legit. I paid a decent amount of money for this. And
a decent amount of money for this. And
a decent amount of money for this. And what you can see here is what they gave
what you can see here is what they gave
what you can see here is what they gave the fair market value. And then if I
the fair market value. And then if I
the fair market value. And then if I scroll down here, I'll be able to show
scroll down here, I'll be able to show
scroll down here, I'll be able to show you what we did during these years. So
you what we did during these years. So
you what we did during these years. So you can see here the SDE, that's seller
you can see here the SDE, that's seller
you can see here the SDE, that's seller discretionary earning. What that means
discretionary earning. What that means
discretionary earning. What that means is that's what the business made in
is that's what the business made in
is that's what the business made in profit including what the owner was
profit including what the owner was
profit including what the owner was paid. And you can see here in 2021 it
paid. And you can see here in 2021 it
paid. And you can see here in 2021 it was 1.3. 2022 1.6. 2023 1.5 and then
was 1.3. 2022 1.6. 2023 1.5 and then
was 1.3. 2022 1.6. 2023 1.5 and then 2024
2024 1.2. And as of right now, we're
1.2. And as of right now, we're
1.2. And as of right now, we're currently at around 561K for this year.
currently at around 561K for this year.
currently at around 561K for this year. And we're doing over $200,000 a month
And we're doing over $200,000 a month
And we're doing over $200,000 a month consistently with very good margins. And
consistently with very good margins. And
consistently with very good margins. And then you can see here um over 6.5
then you can see here um over 6.5
then you can see here um over 6.5 million. And then we switched
million. And then we switched
million. And then we switched processors. You can see this was last
processors. You can see this was last
processors. You can see this was last year and then this is the current year
year and then this is the current year
year and then this is the current year to show you that this is legit. And I
to show you that this is legit. And I
to show you that this is legit. And I can switch this um just do last 90 days.
can switch this um just do last 90 days.
can switch this um just do last 90 days. And you can see that it automatically
And you can see that it automatically
And you can see that it automatically changes. So, the reason why I'm showing
changes. So, the reason why I'm showing
changes. So, the reason why I'm showing you this is because number one, I've
you this is because number one, I've
you this is because number one, I've started doing some research to see what
started doing some research to see what
started doing some research to see what other people are are doing and showing
other people are are doing and showing
other people are are doing and showing people. And I've noticed it doesn't seem
people. And I've noticed it doesn't seem
people. And I've noticed it doesn't seem like a lot of people that actually show
like a lot of people that actually show
like a lot of people that actually show people how to grow
people how to grow
people how to grow agencies. It doesn't seem like they
agencies. It doesn't seem like they
agencies. It doesn't seem like they actually have them or do it. So, this is
actually have them or do it. So, this is
actually have them or do it. So, this is my website. You can see here, this is
my website. You can see here, this is
my website. You can see here, this is literally hundreds of testimonials from
literally hundreds of testimonials from
literally hundreds of testimonials from clients that I've worked with
clients that I've worked with
clients that I've worked with implementing the exact system that I'm
implementing the exact system that I'm
implementing the exact system that I'm going to be going over and breaking down
going to be going over and breaking down
going to be going over and breaking down for you and showing you that have
for you and showing you that have
for you and showing you that have benefited from using it and that have
benefited from using it and that have
benefited from using it and that have used it. And then if I go over here to
used it. And then if I go over here to
used it. And then if I go over here to Google, you can type in gym members now.
Google, you can type in gym members now.
Google, you can type in gym members now. This is my website. This is where we get
This is my website. This is where we get
This is my website. This is where we get reviews. You can even see we got some
reviews. You can even see we got some
reviews. You can even see we got some really good reviews just recently. Uh,
really good reviews just recently. Uh,
really good reviews just recently. Uh, really cool to see. But again, you can
really cool to see. But again, you can
really cool to see. But again, you can see same thing, tons of reviews. This is
see same thing, tons of reviews. This is
see same thing, tons of reviews. This is a legitimate business that provides
a legitimate business that provides
a legitimate business that provides legitimate services to local business
legitimate services to local business
legitimate services to local business owners and their AI based services.
owners and their AI based services.
owners and their AI based services. Okay. So, now that I've gone through
Okay. So, now that I've gone through
Okay. So, now that I've gone through that with you and we're done with that
that with you and we're done with that
that with you and we're done with that and you know that I actually have the
and you know that I actually have the
and you know that I actually have the proof to back up what I'm about to show
proof to back up what I'm about to show
proof to back up what I'm about to show you, I'm going to break down for you
you, I'm going to break down for you
you, I'm going to break down for you guys the services that I offer. And then
guys the services that I offer. And then
guys the services that I offer. And then from there, I'm going to be showing you
from there, I'm going to be showing you
from there, I'm going to be showing you guys what this looks like. But before I
guys what this looks like. But before I
guys what this looks like. But before I kind of do that, one thing I want to
kind of do that, one thing I want to
kind of do that, one thing I want to start with is this quote from Aristotle.
start with is this quote from Aristotle.
start with is this quote from Aristotle. And what he said was, "The whole is
And what he said was, "The whole is
And what he said was, "The whole is greater than the sum of its parts." A
greater than the sum of its parts." A
greater than the sum of its parts." A lot of people are talking about AI
lot of people are talking about AI
lot of people are talking about AI agents this and that and that's great,
agents this and that and that's great,
agents this and that and that's great, but just remember the whole is greater
but just remember the whole is greater
but just remember the whole is greater than the sum of its parts because I'm
than the sum of its parts because I'm
than the sum of its parts because I'm going to break down for you a bunch of
going to break down for you a bunch of
going to break down for you a bunch of different cool things that AI agents can
different cool things that AI agents can
different cool things that AI agents can can do and automations can do and
can do and automations can do and
can do and automations can do and services that people can provide and try
services that people can provide and try
services that people can provide and try and sell to local businesses. But if you
and sell to local businesses. But if you
and sell to local businesses. But if you put them together in the proper way, in
put them together in the proper way, in
put them together in the proper way, in the proper structure, I've already gone
the proper structure, I've already gone
the proper structure, I've already gone through the trial and error of figuring
through the trial and error of figuring
through the trial and error of figuring that out, which I'm going to show you,
that out, which I'm going to show you,
that out, which I'm going to show you, you can really provide local businesses
you can really provide local businesses
you can really provide local businesses with something that's extremely valuable
with something that's extremely valuable
with something that's extremely valuable and extremely impactful on their
and extremely impactful on their
and extremely impactful on their business, which will allow you to build
business, which will allow you to build
business, which will allow you to build a very successful business that you
a very successful business that you
a very successful business that you could potentially roll up with me and
could potentially roll up with me and
could potentially roll up with me and sell for multiple millions of dollars.
sell for multiple millions of dollars.
sell for multiple millions of dollars. So, the first thing is AI re-engaging to
So, the first thing is AI re-engaging to
So, the first thing is AI re-engaging to old leads. And like I said, I'm going to
old leads. And like I said, I'm going to
old leads. And like I said, I'm going to show you guys live examples of this with
show you guys live examples of this with
show you guys live examples of this with clients and the software that I use to
clients and the software that I use to
clients and the software that I use to provide all of these services. But this
provide all of these services. But this
provide all of these services. But this is the first thing, and it's very, very
is the first thing, and it's very, very
is the first thing, and it's very, very simple. A lot of local businesses and a
simple. A lot of local businesses and a
simple. A lot of local businesses and a lot of businesses, they have a ton of
lot of businesses, they have a ton of
lot of businesses, they have a ton of leads and they don't have a a good
leads and they don't have a a good
leads and they don't have a a good process to re-engage these leads that
process to re-engage these leads that
process to re-engage these leads that are in their system. So, let's say, for
are in their system. So, let's say, for
are in their system. So, let's say, for example, if you went to a gym and you
example, if you went to a gym and you
example, if you went to a gym and you tried them out for a 7-day pass. Let's
tried them out for a 7-day pass. Let's
tried them out for a 7-day pass. Let's say they were doing a 7-day promotion.
say they were doing a 7-day promotion.
say they were doing a 7-day promotion. You went in there, you did a trial, and
You went in there, you did a trial, and
You went in there, you did a trial, and you didn't actually end up becoming a
you didn't actually end up becoming a
you didn't actually end up becoming a member. You ended up becoming a member
member. You ended up becoming a member
member. You ended up becoming a member at another gym. And let's say it was
at another gym. And let's say it was
at another gym. And let's say it was about a year ago since you did that
about a year ago since you did that
about a year ago since you did that 7-day trial, and you're at this other
7-day trial, and you're at this other
7-day trial, and you're at this other gym. You're kind of getting sick of that
gym. You're kind of getting sick of that
gym. You're kind of getting sick of that other gym. And then you get a text from
other gym. And then you get a text from
other gym. And then you get a text from that gym that had the 7-day trial
that gym that had the 7-day trial
that gym that had the 7-day trial saying, "Hey, we have a great promotion
saying, "Hey, we have a great promotion
saying, "Hey, we have a great promotion going for men just like you, and you can
going for men just like you, and you can
going for men just like you, and you can get started with us for a month free."
get started with us for a month free."
get started with us for a month free." Right? If you received that text, do you
Right? If you received that text, do you
Right? If you received that text, do you think you'd be likely to
think you'd be likely to
think you'd be likely to maybe go check it out, especially if you
maybe go check it out, especially if you
maybe go check it out, especially if you were maybe not super happy with the gym
were maybe not super happy with the gym
were maybe not super happy with the gym you were at? Of course, cuz it's an
you were at? Of course, cuz it's an
you were at? Of course, cuz it's an incredible offer and you got back in
incredible offer and you got back in
incredible offer and you got back in front of them.
front of them.
front of them. That's exactly what this service is.
That's exactly what this service is.
That's exactly what this service is. It's very, very straightforward. And all
It's very, very straightforward. And all
It's very, very straightforward. And all we're doing is re-engaging leads within
we're doing is re-engaging leads within
we're doing is re-engaging leads within their database because they don't do a
their database because they don't do a
their database because they don't do a good job of it. So, it's very, very
good job of it. So, it's very, very
good job of it. So, it's very, very straightforward. And this is something
straightforward. And this is something
straightforward. And this is something that you can charge decent money for.
that you can charge decent money for.
that you can charge decent money for. But again, we're talking about this. The
But again, we're talking about this. The
But again, we're talking about this. The whole is greater than the sum of its
whole is greater than the sum of its
whole is greater than the sum of its parts, which we're going to get into.
parts, which we're going to get into.
parts, which we're going to get into. So, that's the first thing that you can
So, that's the first thing that you can
So, that's the first thing that you can offer. And before I kind of break this
offer. And before I kind of break this
offer. And before I kind of break this all down, again, you're just taking
all down, again, you're just taking
all down, again, you're just taking their database within the CRM. and
their database within the CRM. and
their database within the CRM. and you're reaching out to them, getting
you're reaching out to them, getting
you're reaching out to them, getting people that are interested to then book
people that are interested to then book
people that are interested to then book an appointment and come in so that you
an appointment and come in so that you
an appointment and come in so that you can turn them into a customer that that
can turn them into a customer that that
can turn them into a customer that that that service-based business, that local
that service-based business, that local
that service-based business, that local business can turn them into a customer.
business can turn them into a customer.
business can turn them into a customer. And so what I'm showing you here, this
And so what I'm showing you here, this
And so what I'm showing you here, this is the software that we use to provide
is the software that we use to provide
is the software that we use to provide all these services. And you can see
all these services. And you can see
all these services. And you can see here, this was one week where we were
here, this was one week where we were
here, this was one week where we were able to generate, I honestly don't know
able to generate, I honestly don't know
able to generate, I honestly don't know how many appointments this is. I don't
how many appointments this is. I don't
how many appointments this is. I don't want to count them, but we were able to
want to count them, but we were able to
want to count them, but we were able to generate this gym owner that we work
generate this gym owner that we work
generate this gym owner that we work with. I think it was over like 70
with. I think it was over like 70
with. I think it was over like 70 appointments in a week. Um, for some
appointments in a week. Um, for some
appointments in a week. Um, for some reason my eyes itching, but we were able
reason my eyes itching, but we were able
reason my eyes itching, but we were able to generate like 70 appointments in one
to generate like 70 appointments in one
to generate like 70 appointments in one week. And if you look at the next week,
week. And if you look at the next week,
week. And if you look at the next week, it wasn't as much, but it was it was a
it wasn't as much, but it was it was a
it wasn't as much, but it was it was a lot. And the best part about this is
lot. And the best part about this is
lot. And the best part about this is that you're not having to spend money on
that you're not having to spend money on
that you're not having to spend money on ads. So, you're able to generate a ton
ads. So, you're able to generate a ton
ads. So, you're able to generate a ton of sales opportunities without investing
of sales opportunities without investing
of sales opportunities without investing any money into marketing for that
any money into marketing for that
any money into marketing for that customer, which is a huge, huge benefit
customer, which is a huge, huge benefit
customer, which is a huge, huge benefit when you're in a world where everyone is
when you're in a world where everyone is
when you're in a world where everyone is screaming, "Run paid ads, spend money on
screaming, "Run paid ads, spend money on
screaming, "Run paid ads, spend money on marketing." With this, we're going to
marketing." With this, we're going to
marketing." With this, we're going to them and saying, "You've got a hot
them and saying, "You've got a hot
them and saying, "You've got a hot database of leads you haven't done
database of leads you haven't done
database of leads you haven't done anything with. Give it to me and let me
anything with. Give it to me and let me
anything with. Give it to me and let me engage it with AI and then nurture these
engage it with AI and then nurture these
engage it with AI and then nurture these leads through the door for you without
leads through the door for you without
leads through the door for you without having to spend any money on ads. I'm
having to spend any money on ads. I'm
having to spend any money on ads. I'm going to be able to get you potentially
going to be able to get you potentially
going to be able to get you potentially hundreds of appointments like we did in
hundreds of appointments like we did in
hundreds of appointments like we did in this example here. literally over 100
this example here. literally over 100
this example here. literally over 100 appointments in two weeks. Right? So
appointments in two weeks. Right? So
appointments in two weeks. Right? So that's the first thing. Okay? And that's
that's the first thing. Okay? And that's
that's the first thing. Okay? And that's what you want to start with as far as
what you want to start with as far as
what you want to start with as far as this sequential system is concerned. You
this sequential system is concerned. You
this sequential system is concerned. You want to start with that because a lot of
want to start with that because a lot of
want to start with that because a lot of these businesses, they have that within
these businesses, they have that within
these businesses, they have that within their database and they haven't done
their database and they haven't done
their database and they haven't done anything with it. So do you think it
anything with it. So do you think it
anything with it. So do you think it makes sense to start running ads for
makes sense to start running ads for
makes sense to start running ads for them generating cold leads or do you
them generating cold leads or do you
them generating cold leads or do you think it makes sense to start with their
think it makes sense to start with their
think it makes sense to start with their database of warm leads that they haven't
database of warm leads that they haven't
database of warm leads that they haven't re-engaged? That might just need a a
re-engaged? That might just need a a
re-engaged? That might just need a a text to come back in where you don't
text to come back in where you don't
text to come back in where you don't have to spend any money on ads. Of
have to spend any money on ads. Of
have to spend any money on ads. Of course, it's going to be this, but a lot
course, it's going to be this, but a lot
course, it's going to be this, but a lot of people neglect this and do not do
of people neglect this and do not do
of people neglect this and do not do this. Okay. The second thing is AI
this. Okay. The second thing is AI
this. Okay. The second thing is AI reviews and referrals. So, all we're
reviews and referrals. So, all we're
reviews and referrals. So, all we're doing with this is re-engaging active
doing with this is re-engaging active
doing with this is re-engaging active customers of these local businesses and
customers of these local businesses and
customers of these local businesses and asking them for reviews. That's it. But
asking them for reviews. That's it. But
asking them for reviews. That's it. But what we're doing that's different from
what we're doing that's different from
what we're doing that's different from other companies that provide this
other companies that provide this
other companies that provide this service as a standalone service is we're
service as a standalone service is we're
service as a standalone service is we're leveraging an offer, a powerful offer to
leveraging an offer, a powerful offer to
leveraging an offer, a powerful offer to to get a really high response rate when
to get a really high response rate when
to get a really high response rate when we're asking people for reviews. So,
we're asking people for reviews. So,
we're asking people for reviews. So, instead of reaching out to someone and
instead of reaching out to someone and
instead of reaching out to someone and saying, "Hey, hope you've enjoyed, you
saying, "Hey, hope you've enjoyed, you
saying, "Hey, hope you've enjoyed, you know, working out at our gym. Would you
know, working out at our gym. Would you
know, working out at our gym. Would you mind leaving us a review?" We're going
mind leaving us a review?" We're going
mind leaving us a review?" We're going to say, "If you'd like a chance to win a
to say, "If you'd like a chance to win a
to say, "If you'd like a chance to win a membership for free for the year, just
membership for free for the year, just
membership for free for the year, just let us know how your experience has
let us know how your experience has
let us know how your experience has been. We'd really value your feedback."
been. We'd really value your feedback."
been. We'd really value your feedback." By doing that, we get over 200% more
By doing that, we get over 200% more
By doing that, we get over 200% more people responding and obviously saying
people responding and obviously saying
people responding and obviously saying positive things. And then from the
positive things. And then from the
positive things. And then from the people that say positive things, we ask
people that say positive things, we ask
people that say positive things, we ask them to leave a review. the people that
them to leave a review. the people that
them to leave a review. the people that leave reviews, we then ask them if
leave reviews, we then ask them if
leave reviews, we then ask them if they'd like to bring friends and family
they'd like to bring friends and family
they'd like to bring friends and family in with another powerful offer. And then
in with another powerful offer. And then
in with another powerful offer. And then we tie it back to that initial offer
we tie it back to that initial offer
we tie it back to that initial offer where they have a chance to win a
where they have a chance to win a
where they have a chance to win a membership for free and say, "Anyone you
membership for free and say, "Anyone you
membership for free and say, "Anyone you bring in that comes from you, we'll put
bring in that comes from you, we'll put
bring in that comes from you, we'll put your name into that raffle for a chance
your name into that raffle for a chance
your name into that raffle for a chance to win that free membership again so
to win that free membership again so
to win that free membership again so that you have a higher opportunity to
that you have a higher opportunity to
that you have a higher opportunity to actually win that." And then we allow
actually win that." And then we allow
actually win that." And then we allow them to bring friends and family in on a
them to bring friends and family in on a
them to bring friends and family in on a trial. So, by doing this, we're able to
trial. So, by doing this, we're able to
trial. So, by doing this, we're able to generate tons of reviews on Google for
generate tons of reviews on Google for
generate tons of reviews on Google for the customer and tons of referrals,
the customer and tons of referrals,
the customer and tons of referrals, which are free leads. Once again, not
which are free leads. Once again, not
which are free leads. Once again, not having to spend money on advertising.
having to spend money on advertising.
having to spend money on advertising. And now again, if you think about this,
And now again, if you think about this,
And now again, if you think about this, a lot of people out there in the
a lot of people out there in the
a lot of people out there in the marketplace are screaming and shouting
marketplace are screaming and shouting
marketplace are screaming and shouting basic AI agents, simple workflows, but
basic AI agents, simple workflows, but
basic AI agents, simple workflows, but they're not stacking these things in a
they're not stacking these things in a
they're not stacking these things in a system sequentially where it produces a
system sequentially where it produces a
system sequentially where it produces a really great result for the customer,
really great result for the customer,
really great result for the customer, which in turn allows you to retain them,
which in turn allows you to retain them,
which in turn allows you to retain them, charge a lot of money, and get them
charge a lot of money, and get them
charge a lot of money, and get them telling their friends about you so that
telling their friends about you so that
telling their friends about you so that you're able to grow through word of
you're able to grow through word of
you're able to grow through word of mouth, not paid ads. Okay. So, let me
mouth, not paid ads. Okay. So, let me
mouth, not paid ads. Okay. So, let me show you an example of what this looks
show you an example of what this looks
show you an example of what this looks like within the same software. And you
like within the same software. And you
like within the same software. And you can see for this specific gym, we were
can see for this specific gym, we were
can see for this specific gym, we were able to get, we've only been working
able to get, we've only been working
able to get, we've only been working with them for 48 days now. We've been
with them for 48 days now. We've been
with them for 48 days now. We've been able to get 76 positive responses from
able to get 76 positive responses from
able to get 76 positive responses from the people we've reached out to. We have
the people we've reached out to. We have
the people we've reached out to. We have thousands of other people we haven't yet
thousands of other people we haven't yet
thousands of other people we haven't yet reached out to. It's just you want a
reached out to. It's just you want a
reached out to. It's just you want a slow trickle in when it comes to getting
slow trickle in when it comes to getting
slow trickle in when it comes to getting reviews. You don't want to get a major
reviews. You don't want to get a major
reviews. You don't want to get a major influx of reviews. I'm sure you've
influx of reviews. I'm sure you've
influx of reviews. I'm sure you've probably seen a a Google business page
probably seen a a Google business page
probably seen a a Google business page before and you see just a bunch of
before and you see just a bunch of
before and you see just a bunch of reviews all at once and then none for
reviews all at once and then none for
reviews all at once and then none for multiple months. It's a subconscious red
multiple months. It's a subconscious red
multiple months. It's a subconscious red flag that gets raised. So, you don't
flag that gets raised. So, you don't
flag that gets raised. So, you don't want that and Google doesn't like that
want that and Google doesn't like that
want that and Google doesn't like that either when it comes to ranking. But,
either when it comes to ranking. But,
either when it comes to ranking. But, nonetheless, you can see they had 76
nonetheless, you can see they had 76
nonetheless, you can see they had 76 positive responses. They had 24 people
positive responses. They had 24 people
positive responses. They had 24 people leave reviews. But then really, most
leave reviews. But then really, most
leave reviews. But then really, most importantly, they had seven people
importantly, they had seven people
importantly, they had seven people become referrals without them having to
become referrals without them having to
become referrals without them having to spend any money in advertising. And then
spend any money in advertising. And then
spend any money in advertising. And then you can see here negative response for
you can see here negative response for
you can see here negative response for any of the people that say they had a
any of the people that say they had a
any of the people that say they had a bad experience when we do initially ask
bad experience when we do initially ask
bad experience when we do initially ask them for their feedback. We don't ask
them for their feedback. We don't ask
them for their feedback. We don't ask them for a review, right? So we're only
them for a review, right? So we're only
them for a review, right? So we're only generating five star reviews by doing
generating five star reviews by doing
generating five star reviews by doing this. Sometimes four stars, but mainly
this. Sometimes four stars, but mainly
this. Sometimes four stars, but mainly five star because anyone that says a
five star because anyone that says a
five star because anyone that says a neutral or negative response in that
neutral or negative response in that
neutral or negative response in that initial message, we just push them to a
initial message, we just push them to a
initial message, we just push them to a feedback form where they can leave their
feedback form where they can leave their
feedback form where they can leave their feedback. Okay. So that is the second
feedback. Okay. So that is the second
feedback. Okay. So that is the second thing that we offer. And again, this is
thing that we offer. And again, this is
thing that we offer. And again, this is very, very simple, very easy to provide.
very, very simple, very easy to provide.
very, very simple, very easy to provide. It's literally automated. But first
It's literally automated. But first
It's literally automated. But first thing we're doing is we're reaching out
thing we're doing is we're reaching out
thing we're doing is we're reaching out to them, asking for their feedback,
to them, asking for their feedback,
to them, asking for their feedback, right? If they have positive feedback
right? If they have positive feedback
right? If they have positive feedback from there, we're asking for review. And
from there, we're asking for review. And
from there, we're asking for review. And then after they leave a review, we're
then after they leave a review, we're
then after they leave a review, we're asking if they'd like to bring friends
asking if they'd like to bring friends
asking if they'd like to bring friends and family in, letting them know that
and family in, letting them know that
and family in, letting them know that they have something to gain and so does
they have something to gain and so does
they have something to gain and so does their friend or family member. And by
their friend or family member. And by
their friend or family member. And by doing that, we're generating free leads.
doing that, we're generating free leads.
doing that, we're generating free leads. The third thing you can do is website
The third thing you can do is website
The third thing you can do is website lead nurturing, which is very simple.
lead nurturing, which is very simple.
lead nurturing, which is very simple. All it is is when people go to a
All it is is when people go to a
All it is is when people go to a website, let's say for example, I go to,
website, let's say for example, I go to,
website, let's say for example, I go to, let's just look up gym near
let's just look up gym near
let's just look up gym near me, right? So, if I go to Off the Grid
me, right? So, if I go to Off the Grid
me, right? So, if I go to Off the Grid Fitness, let's
Fitness, let's
Fitness, let's see, they're going to have a form on
see, they're going to have a form on
see, they're going to have a form on their website, right? Oh, they really
their website, right? Oh, they really
their website, right? Oh, they really need help. It doesn't even look like
need help. It doesn't even look like
need help. It doesn't even look like they have a forum. This is really bad.
they have a forum. This is really bad.
they have a forum. This is really bad. This This is definitely somebody that
This This is definitely somebody that
This This is definitely somebody that you could help if you were trying to
you could help if you were trying to
you could help if you were trying to literally just take my process. But you
literally just take my process. But you
literally just take my process. But you can see here, first name, last name,
can see here, first name, last name,
can see here, first name, last name, email, phone number. So what happens
email, phone number. So what happens
email, phone number. So what happens from here is you you submit your
from here is you you submit your
from here is you you submit your information and now that lead needs to
information and now that lead needs to
information and now that lead needs to be followed up with, right? A lot of
be followed up with, right? A lot of
be followed up with, right? A lot of these local businesses do not have a
these local businesses do not have a
these local businesses do not have a good process to follow up with leads.
good process to follow up with leads.
good process to follow up with leads. And Harvard did a study back in 2018 and
And Harvard did a study back in 2018 and
And Harvard did a study back in 2018 and what they found was if you're not
what they found was if you're not
what they found was if you're not following up with leads within 5
following up with leads within 5
following up with leads within 5 minutes, the chances of getting them
minutes, the chances of getting them
minutes, the chances of getting them through your door or converting them
through your door or converting them
through your door or converting them into a customer can drop over 400%. And
into a customer can drop over 400%. And
into a customer can drop over 400%. And this was in 2018. Look the study up.
this was in 2018. Look the study up.
this was in 2018. Look the study up. It's there. There's some other really
It's there. There's some other really
It's there. There's some other really cool data when it comes to speed to
cool data when it comes to speed to
cool data when it comes to speed to lead, best times to contact leads to get
lead, best times to contact leads to get
lead, best times to contact leads to get the highest answer rate and response
the highest answer rate and response
the highest answer rate and response rate. But because of that, you can
rate. But because of that, you can
rate. But because of that, you can easily test out these local businesses
easily test out these local businesses
easily test out these local businesses like this one, and I guarantee you they
like this one, and I guarantee you they
like this one, and I guarantee you they wouldn't get back to me until middle of
wouldn't get back to me until middle of
wouldn't get back to me until middle of day tomorrow, uh maybe early morning.
day tomorrow, uh maybe early morning.
day tomorrow, uh maybe early morning. But still, when I have a system like
But still, when I have a system like
But still, when I have a system like this, they're going to get followed up
this, they're going to get followed up
this, they're going to get followed up with immediately and they're going to
with immediately and they're going to
with immediately and they're going to get booked in for an appointment
get booked in for an appointment
get booked in for an appointment immediately because if you're not,
immediately because if you're not,
immediately because if you're not, they're going to go somewhere else and
they're going to go somewhere else and
they're going to go somewhere else and the person that gets back to them first
the person that gets back to them first
the person that gets back to them first is probably going to win. So, so the
is probably going to win. So, so the
is probably going to win. So, so the fifth thing is paid ads with AI lead
fifth thing is paid ads with AI lead
fifth thing is paid ads with AI lead nurturing. And the reason why I'm saying
nurturing. And the reason why I'm saying
nurturing. And the reason why I'm saying three and five are somewhat similar is
three and five are somewhat similar is
three and five are somewhat similar is because they are when you're running
because they are when you're running
because they are when you're running paid ads, you're sending traffic to a
paid ads, you're sending traffic to a
paid ads, you're sending traffic to a website. So that's all you're doing is
website. So that's all you're doing is
website. So that's all you're doing is you're putting an offer out there,
you're putting an offer out there,
you're putting an offer out there, capturing people's
capturing people's
capturing people's interest, funneling that traffic to a
interest, funneling that traffic to a
interest, funneling that traffic to a website where they can then submit their
website where they can then submit their
website where they can then submit their information like we showed you on this
information like we showed you on this
information like we showed you on this really poorly built landing page. But
really poorly built landing page. But
really poorly built landing page. But now, if I go over here, what you're
now, if I go over here, what you're
now, if I go over here, what you're going to see is a landing page that
going to see is a landing page that
going to see is a landing page that we've built. And you're going to see ads
we've built. And you're going to see ads
we've built. And you're going to see ads that we're running for a customer. So,
that we're running for a customer. So,
that we're running for a customer. So, if I were to to see one of these ads and
if I were to to see one of these ads and
if I were to to see one of these ads and then click on it, I'm going to be taken
then click on it, I'm going to be taken
then click on it, I'm going to be taken to this landing page or a website. And
to this landing page or a website. And
to this landing page or a website. And from here, I would fill out my
from here, I would fill out my
from here, I would fill out my information. Once I click this reserve
information. Once I click this reserve
information. Once I click this reserve spot button, what's going to happen is
spot button, what's going to happen is
spot button, what's going to happen is I'm going to receive a text from my
I'm going to receive a text from my
I'm going to receive a text from my system. Okay? And here's what this looks
system. Okay? And here's what this looks
system. Okay? And here's what this looks like. So, if I go all the way up here to
like. So, if I go all the way up here to
like. So, if I go all the way up here to the top, you can see,
the top, you can see,
the top, you can see, hey, time
hey, time
hey, time fitness, can't wait to meet you on
fitness, can't wait to meet you on
fitness, can't wait to meet you on Friday, January 24th at 11:00 a.m.,
Friday, January 24th at 11:00 a.m.,
Friday, January 24th at 11:00 a.m., okay? Because in this example, after
okay? Because in this example, after
okay? Because in this example, after this guy submitted his information, he
this guy submitted his information, he
this guy submitted his information, he was taken to a calendar page to schedule
was taken to a calendar page to schedule
was taken to a calendar page to schedule an appointment, just like I'm sure you
an appointment, just like I'm sure you
an appointment, just like I'm sure you guys have probably gone through before,
guys have probably gone through before,
guys have probably gone through before, and he decided to book an appointment.
and he decided to book an appointment.
and he decided to book an appointment. So, he received that text confirming
So, he received that text confirming
So, he received that text confirming that appointment right away. If he
that appointment right away. If he
that appointment right away. If he hadn't booked an appointment, if he had
hadn't booked an appointment, if he had
hadn't booked an appointment, if he had bounced, let's say he submitted his
bounced, let's say he submitted his
bounced, let's say he submitted his information and then exited out of the
information and then exited out of the
information and then exited out of the page, he would have still received a
page, he would have still received a
page, he would have still received a text right away saying,
"Hey, I saw you. I saw I saw you showed
"Hey, I saw you. I saw I saw you showed interest for taking advantage of our
interest for taking advantage of our
interest for taking advantage of our limited time promotion. When can you
limited time promotion. When can you
limited time promotion. When can you come in to claim it? We're running out."
come in to claim it? We're running out."
come in to claim it? We're running out." Right? So, that's what they would have
Right? So, that's what they would have
Right? So, that's what they would have received. But then you can see here,
received. But then you can see here,
received. But then you can see here, we're working the lead. We're following
we're working the lead. We're following
we're working the lead. We're following up with them. This is a pretty long
up with them. This is a pretty long
up with them. This is a pretty long conversation actually because they
conversation actually because they
conversation actually because they weren't actually able to show up to
weren't actually able to show up to
weren't actually able to show up to their appointment. But we're doing this
their appointment. But we're doing this
their appointment. But we're doing this all done for the customer without them
all done for the customer without them
all done for the customer without them having to do any of it on their own,
having to do any of it on their own,
having to do any of it on their own, without them having to have their staff
without them having to have their staff
without them having to have their staff do it. And because of that, it's a
do it. And because of that, it's a
do it. And because of that, it's a massive advantage because they're not
massive advantage because they're not
massive advantage because they're not going to follow up with their leads
going to follow up with their leads
going to follow up with their leads fast. They're just not. Test out a gym,
fast. They're just not. Test out a gym,
fast. They're just not. Test out a gym, test out a chiropractor, test out a
test out a chiropractor, test out a
test out a chiropractor, test out a dentist, test them all out. Submit your
dentist, test them all out. Submit your
dentist, test them all out. Submit your information, see how long it takes them
information, see how long it takes them
information, see how long it takes them to get back to you. test out an HVAC
to get back to you. test out an HVAC
to get back to you. test out an HVAC company, right? It's probably going to
company, right? It's probably going to
company, right? It's probably going to be a little bit, especially if you opt
be a little bit, especially if you opt
be a little bit, especially if you opt in later at night. But because we're
in later at night. But because we're
in later at night. But because we're doing this for them and we're doing it
doing this for them and we're doing it
doing this for them and we're doing it right away, they don't have to worry
right away, they don't have to worry
right away, they don't have to worry about it. And the money they're
about it. And the money they're
about it. And the money they're investing into marketing is going to
investing into marketing is going to
investing into marketing is going to generate a massive return compared to
generate a massive return compared to
generate a massive return compared to what they would get otherwise. So, you
what they would get otherwise. So, you
what they would get otherwise. So, you can see here, the person said they
can see here, the person said they
can see here, the person said they showed up, right? So, they they showed
showed up, right? So, they they showed
showed up, right? So, they they showed up and the client didn't have to do
up and the client didn't have to do
up and the client didn't have to do anything to make that happen. So, this
anything to make that happen. So, this
anything to make that happen. So, this is extremely powerful. But more
is extremely powerful. But more
is extremely powerful. But more important before I get to step four is
important before I get to step four is
important before I get to step four is that if we just look at the flow of this
that if we just look at the flow of this
that if we just look at the flow of this and how this all works together. Instead
and how this all works together. Instead
and how this all works together. Instead of just selling one of these things
of just selling one of these things
of just selling one of these things independently, we're actually selling
independently, we're actually selling
independently, we're actually selling them all collectively but in a in the
them all collectively but in a in the
them all collectively but in a in the proper order. So instead of just saying,
proper order. So instead of just saying,
proper order. So instead of just saying, "Hey, we're going to re-engage old
"Hey, we're going to re-engage old
"Hey, we're going to re-engage old leads. We're going to get you reviews.
leads. We're going to get you reviews.
leads. We're going to get you reviews. We're going to get you referrals. We're
We're going to get you referrals. We're
We're going to get you referrals. We're going to run ads. We're going to follow
going to run ads. We're going to follow
going to run ads. We're going to follow up with your leads. We're going to do
up with your leads. We're going to do
up with your leads. We're going to do that all at once." We're saying no. The
that all at once." We're saying no. The
that all at once." We're saying no. The smartest and most efficient thing to do
smartest and most efficient thing to do
smartest and most efficient thing to do would be to re-engage your old leads
would be to re-engage your old leads
would be to re-engage your old leads before we spend money in advertising
before we spend money in advertising
before we spend money in advertising because we're going to be able to see
because we're going to be able to see
because we're going to be able to see number one, how do you guys do at
number one, how do you guys do at
number one, how do you guys do at converting the promotion that we're
converting the promotion that we're
converting the promotion that we're running to the old list, but number two,
running to the old list, but number two,
running to the old list, but number two, knowing you guys are good at closing,
knowing you guys are good at closing,
knowing you guys are good at closing, right? Wink wink. A lot of these local
right? Wink wink. A lot of these local
right? Wink wink. A lot of these local business owners claim to be great at
business owners claim to be great at
business owners claim to be great at closing. We're going to tell them, we're
closing. We're going to tell them, we're
closing. We're going to tell them, we're going to take that money that you
going to take that money that you
going to take that money that you collect, the capital you generate from
collect, the capital you generate from
collect, the capital you generate from these sales where we're not spending any
these sales where we're not spending any
these sales where we're not spending any money in marketing, and then we're going
money in marketing, and then we're going
money in marketing, and then we're going to reinvest that money into paid ads,
to reinvest that money into paid ads,
to reinvest that money into paid ads, okay? But we're not going to do that
okay? But we're not going to do that
okay? But we're not going to do that until we've started to generate you
until we've started to generate you
until we've started to generate you reviews and referrals because when
reviews and referrals because when
reviews and referrals because when people see ads, 70 to 80% of people will
people see ads, 70 to 80% of people will
people see ads, 70 to 80% of people will actually reference Google to see what
actually reference Google to see what
actually reference Google to see what other people are saying. And this is
other people are saying. And this is
other people are saying. And this is according to a bunch of different
according to a bunch of different
according to a bunch of different studies. So because of that, what you
studies. So because of that, what you
studies. So because of that, what you want is to have a nice warmed up Google
want is to have a nice warmed up Google
want is to have a nice warmed up Google My Business storefront that looks good
My Business storefront that looks good
My Business storefront that looks good because if you don't, the money you're
because if you don't, the money you're
because if you don't, the money you're investing into your marketing will only
investing into your marketing will only
investing into your marketing will only generate a fraction of what you could
generate a fraction of what you could
generate a fraction of what you could have generated if you had done this.
have generated if you had done this.
have generated if you had done this. Okay, so now the sequential order is
Okay, so now the sequential order is
Okay, so now the sequential order is starting to make sense, right? We're
starting to make sense, right? We're
starting to make sense, right? We're going to reach out to the old leads
going to reach out to the old leads
going to reach out to the old leads without spending any money. We're going
without spending any money. We're going
without spending any money. We're going to get reviews going before we start
to get reviews going before we start
to get reviews going before we start investing money into ads because people
investing money into ads because people
investing money into ads because people will be looking that business up when
will be looking that business up when
will be looking that business up when they see their ads. And by doing that,
they see their ads. And by doing that,
they see their ads. And by doing that, by the time we get to the ads, that
by the time we get to the ads, that
by the time we get to the ads, that client's going to have generated capital
client's going to have generated capital
client's going to have generated capital without investing any money into ads.
without investing any money into ads.
without investing any money into ads. And now their ads are going to perform
And now their ads are going to perform
And now their ads are going to perform better than they ever did before if they
better than they ever did before if they
better than they ever did before if they had worked with another company because
had worked with another company because
had worked with another company because they have a more validated Google My
they have a more validated Google My
they have a more validated Google My Business page than they've ever had. And
Business page than they've ever had. And
Business page than they've ever had. And the other benefit that I haven't
the other benefit that I haven't
the other benefit that I haven't discussed when it comes to getting
discussed when it comes to getting
discussed when it comes to getting reviews is if a Google business page is
reviews is if a Google business page is
reviews is if a Google business page is getting a lot of positive reviews
getting a lot of positive reviews
getting a lot of positive reviews frequently, it increases their organic
frequently, it increases their organic
frequently, it increases their organic SEO. And all that stands for is search
SEO. And all that stands for is search
SEO. And all that stands for is search engine optimization. And what that means
engine optimization. And what that means
engine optimization. And what that means is if you looked up on Google gym near
is if you looked up on Google gym near
is if you looked up on Google gym near me and let's say you owned a gym in your
me and let's say you owned a gym in your
me and let's say you owned a gym in your area, you're going your gym is going to
area, you're going your gym is going to
area, you're going your gym is going to rank higher organically for that search
rank higher organically for that search
rank higher organically for that search term and other search terms like it
term and other search terms like it
term and other search terms like it because you're getting more positive
because you're getting more positive
because you're getting more positive engagement on your Google My Business
engagement on your Google My Business
engagement on your Google My Business page. Pretty straightforward. But
page. Pretty straightforward. But
page. Pretty straightforward. But because of that, again, people the the
because of that, again, people the the
because of that, again, people the the money that these clients are going to
money that these clients are going to
money that these clients are going to invest into their ads are going to
invest into their ads are going to
invest into their ads are going to generate a
generate a
generate a significant increase compared to what
significant increase compared to what
significant increase compared to what they would have otherwise. So, it's very
they would have otherwise. So, it's very
they would have otherwise. So, it's very very important that you do it in this
very important that you do it in this
very important that you do it in this order because it crushes people when
order because it crushes people when
order because it crushes people when you're trying to sell them because no
you're trying to sell them because no
you're trying to sell them because no one else does it like this. And it's
one else does it like this. And it's
one else does it like this. And it's very very difficult for a a prospect, a
very very difficult for a a prospect, a
very very difficult for a a prospect, a local business owner to say no to this
local business owner to say no to this
local business owner to say no to this system because no one's doing it. It's
system because no one's doing it. It's
system because no one's doing it. It's so effective and it's something they've
so effective and it's something they've
so effective and it's something they've never heard before. And it's really
never heard before. And it's really
never heard before. And it's really taken me it's taken me up to 5 years to
taken me it's taken me up to 5 years to
taken me it's taken me up to 5 years to actually kind of get this system dialed
actually kind of get this system dialed
actually kind of get this system dialed in, how to communicate it properly. But
in, how to communicate it properly. But
in, how to communicate it properly. But if you do it, it's um it's pretty crazy.
if you do it, it's um it's pretty crazy.
if you do it, it's um it's pretty crazy. And then the little kind of cherry on
And then the little kind of cherry on
And then the little kind of cherry on top, a very very new one which very few
top, a very very new one which very few
top, a very very new one which very few people are doing is an AI agent to
people are doing is an AI agent to
people are doing is an AI agent to answer calls. And so the way we do it is
answer calls. And so the way we do it is
answer calls. And so the way we do it is we have it where it answers the phone.
we have it where it answers the phone.
we have it where it answers the phone. We allow the phone to ring for 10
We allow the phone to ring for 10
We allow the phone to ring for 10 seconds and then it picks the phone up
seconds and then it picks the phone up
seconds and then it picks the phone up to book in customers for consultations
to book in customers for consultations
to book in customers for consultations or tours or to claim an offer that that
or tours or to claim an offer that that
or tours or to claim an offer that that Jim is promoting. And so I'll show you
Jim is promoting. And so I'll show you
Jim is promoting. And so I'll show you guys an example of what this looks like.
guys an example of what this looks like.
guys an example of what this looks like. The craziest thing about this is when we
The craziest thing about this is when we
The craziest thing about this is when we started connecting this to gyms, we
started connecting this to gyms, we
started connecting this to gyms, we found some pretty crazy results. And
found some pretty crazy results. And
found some pretty crazy results. And what what we found is this. This is my
what what we found is this. This is my
what what we found is this. This is my backend uh dashboard for a client of
backend uh dashboard for a client of
backend uh dashboard for a client of mine when it comes to the AI agent. And
mine when it comes to the AI agent. And
mine when it comes to the AI agent. And what you can see here is this is
what you can see here is this is
what you can see here is this is December 18th to January 17th. Okay. So,
December 18th to January 17th. Okay. So,
December 18th to January 17th. Okay. So, I'm going to apply this and then it's
I'm going to apply this and then it's
I'm going to apply this and then it's going to update their numbers. And what
going to update their numbers. And what
going to update their numbers. And what it's going to show us is this. So, if
it's going to show us is this. So, if
it's going to show us is this. So, if you see here where it says new member,
you see here where it says new member,
you see here where it says new member, no answer, new member answered. All that
no answer, new member answered. All that
no answer, new member answered. All that means is out of 90 calls that they had
means is out of 90 calls that they had
means is out of 90 calls that they had from potential new members. So, not
from potential new members. So, not
from potential new members. So, not customers, but people that were not
customers, but people that were not
customers, but people that were not customers, people that were wanting to
customers, people that were wanting to
customers, people that were wanting to become customers, the gym before we
become customers, the gym before we
become customers, the gym before we connected the AI only answered eight out
connected the AI only answered eight out
connected the AI only answered eight out of 90. So, let that sit in sink in. In
of 90. So, let that sit in sink in. In
of 90. So, let that sit in sink in. In 30 days, they had 90 calls from people
30 days, they had 90 calls from people
30 days, they had 90 calls from people that were not customers looking to
that were not customers looking to
that were not customers looking to become customers and their staff only
become customers and their staff only
become customers and their staff only answered
answered
answered eight. Right? So, if you do if you
eight. Right? So, if you do if you
eight. Right? So, if you do if you extrapolate that out over the course of
extrapolate that out over the course of
extrapolate that out over the course of a year, you're looking at almost a
a year, you're looking at almost a
a year, you're looking at almost a thousand calls where the staff could be
thousand calls where the staff could be
thousand calls where the staff could be missing 800 8 almost 900 calls. That's
missing 800 8 almost 900 calls. That's
missing 800 8 almost 900 calls. That's insane. And so the solution we're
insane. And so the solution we're
insane. And so the solution we're providing is we guarantee a 100% of your
providing is we guarantee a 100% of your
providing is we guarantee a 100% of your calls get answered and that our AI will
calls get answered and that our AI will
calls get answered and that our AI will book between 20 to 30% of those calls.
book between 20 to 30% of those calls.
book between 20 to 30% of those calls. So again, if you extrapolate that out,
So again, if you extrapolate that out,
So again, if you extrapolate that out, you're looking at getting an additional
you're looking at getting an additional
you're looking at getting an additional 200 to 400 calls a year with this AI.
200 to 400 calls a year with this AI.
200 to 400 calls a year with this AI. And it's not going to it's not going to
And it's not going to it's not going to
And it's not going to it's not going to require them to do anything additional
require them to do anything additional
require them to do anything additional to what they're already doing. And the
to what they're already doing. And the
to what they're already doing. And the coolest thing about this is it it
coolest thing about this is it it
coolest thing about this is it it literally works 24/7. So, we have it.
literally works 24/7. So, we have it.
literally works 24/7. So, we have it. It's booked appointments literally at
It's booked appointments literally at
It's booked appointments literally at 3:00 a.m. So, what I'm going to show you
3:00 a.m. So, what I'm going to show you
3:00 a.m. So, what I'm going to show you here is an actual example of it booking
here is an actual example of it booking
here is an actual example of it booking an appointment. Okay. So, if I go over
an appointment. Okay. So, if I go over
an appointment. Okay. So, if I go over to the activities, go to calls, this is
to the activities, go to calls, this is
to the activities, go to calls, this is where you can see just appointments
where you can see just appointments
where you can see just appointments getting booked uh from the AI agent for
getting booked uh from the AI agent for
getting booked uh from the AI agent for my clients. So you can see here it's
my clients. So you can see here it's
my clients. So you can see here it's booking hundreds of appointments
booking hundreds of appointments
booking hundreds of appointments 24/7 without the staff or me having to
24/7 without the staff or me having to
24/7 without the staff or me having to do anything which is obviously amazing
do anything which is obviously amazing
do anything which is obviously amazing and and making a lot of money doing it
and and making a lot of money doing it
and and making a lot of money doing it with really not doing much. So if I go
with really not doing much. So if I go
with really not doing much. So if I go over here and go to filter and then I go
over here and go to filter and then I go
over here and go to filter and then I go to tags and type in
to tags and type in
to tags and type in AI, it's going to tag the calls that the
AI, it's going to tag the calls that the
AI, it's going to tag the calls that the AI handled. And you can see here is an
AI handled. And you can see here is an
AI handled. And you can see here is an example of a call where we were actually
example of a call where we were actually
example of a call where we were actually able to book an appointment. And this
able to book an appointment. And this
able to book an appointment. And this was literally just just today.
This is Bitbot, your AI receptionist.
This is Bitbot, your AI receptionist. While our team is busy, I'm here to
While our team is busy, I'm here to
While our team is busy, I'm here to answer any questions and schedule your
answer any questions and schedule your
answer any questions and schedule your free consultation. How can I help you
free consultation. How can I help you
free consultation. How can I help you today?
today?
today? I want to activate my free 7-day
Great. To get started, could I have your
Great. To get started, could I have your first? Okay. So, now it's going to get
first? Okay. So, now it's going to get
first? Okay. So, now it's going to get the contacts information. It's going to
the contacts information. It's going to
the contacts information. It's going to get their phone number and then it's
get their phone number and then it's
get their phone number and then it's going to schedule them in for that
going to schedule them in for that
going to schedule them in for that consultation without the staff having to
consultation without the staff having to
consultation without the staff having to lift a finger to do it. So, by providing
lift a finger to do it. So, by providing
lift a finger to do it. So, by providing all of these services, right, we're able
all of these services, right, we're able
all of these services, right, we're able to create a system that works very, very
to create a system that works very, very
to create a system that works very, very well together where the whole is greater
well together where the whole is greater
well together where the whole is greater than the sum of its parts. And now if I
than the sum of its parts. And now if I
than the sum of its parts. And now if I zoom out right to look at this, you can
zoom out right to look at this, you can
zoom out right to look at this, you can see that I've put all of these things
see that I've put all of these things
see that I've put all of these things together that we just went over. And we
together that we just went over. And we
together that we just went over. And we have sales coaching here, which is it's
have sales coaching here, which is it's
have sales coaching here, which is it's a side thing. You can offer this. It's
a side thing. You can offer this. It's
a side thing. You can offer this. It's something that we do provide. Not for
something that we do provide. Not for
something that we do provide. Not for all of our clients, but it's something
all of our clients, but it's something
all of our clients, but it's something that we do provide because it just helps
that we do provide because it just helps
that we do provide because it just helps us with this whole process, right? We're
us with this whole process, right? We're
us with this whole process, right? We're looking at generating leads, booking
looking at generating leads, booking
looking at generating leads, booking appointments, getting people to show up,
appointments, getting people to show up,
appointments, getting people to show up, and then converting those appointments.
and then converting those appointments.
and then converting those appointments. So, we're helping with the whole gambit.
So, we're helping with the whole gambit.
So, we're helping with the whole gambit. If you don't help with that, it's no big
If you don't help with that, it's no big
If you don't help with that, it's no big deal. I I didn't for the first three
deal. I I didn't for the first three
deal. I I didn't for the first three years and made tons of money. So, it's
years and made tons of money. So, it's
years and made tons of money. So, it's not something you have to do, but I
not something you have to do, but I
not something you have to do, but I included it in here. And the most
included it in here. And the most
included it in here. And the most important thing here again is you can
important thing here again is you can
important thing here again is you can sell these services as standalone
sell these services as standalone
sell these services as standalone services, but you're not going to make
services, but you're not going to make
services, but you're not going to make near as much money as you could. And
near as much money as you could. And
near as much money as you could. And more importantly, you're not going to
more importantly, you're not going to
more importantly, you're not going to have a legitimate business. It's kind of
have a legitimate business. It's kind of
have a legitimate business. It's kind of funny how a lot of people seem to be
funny how a lot of people seem to be
funny how a lot of people seem to be talking about you can make money with an
talking about you can make money with an
talking about you can make money with an AI agent. You can make money with these
AI agent. You can make money with these
AI agent. You can make money with these simple automations. You can make some
simple automations. You can make some
simple automations. You can make some money um a couple thousand bucks or a
money um a couple thousand bucks or a
money um a couple thousand bucks or a couple hundred bucks, but you can't
couple hundred bucks, but you can't
couple hundred bucks, but you can't build a reoccurring based business where
build a reoccurring based business where
build a reoccurring based business where people keep paying you month over month
people keep paying you month over month
people keep paying you month over month over month. Um and if they do and you're
over month. Um and if they do and you're
over month. Um and if they do and you're just providing one, you don't have much
just providing one, you don't have much
just providing one, you don't have much of a competitive edge, right? If if
of a competitive edge, right? If if
of a competitive edge, right? If if you're helping a customer, let's say you
you're helping a customer, let's say you
you're helping a customer, let's say you have an AI answering service and you're
have an AI answering service and you're
have an AI answering service and you're providing that customer with it. And
providing that customer with it. And
providing that customer with it. And then I come in and I say, I can do that.
then I come in and I say, I can do that.
then I come in and I say, I can do that. I can re-engage your old leads for you.
I can re-engage your old leads for you.
I can re-engage your old leads for you. I can generate your reviews and
I can generate your reviews and
I can generate your reviews and referrals for you without you or your
referrals for you without you or your
referrals for you without you or your team having to do it at all or lift a
team having to do it at all or lift a
team having to do it at all or lift a finger, call, text, or email anyone.
finger, call, text, or email anyone.
finger, call, text, or email anyone. I'll nurture all all your website leads
I'll nurture all all your website leads
I'll nurture all all your website leads for you where you guys don't have to do
for you where you guys don't have to do
for you where you guys don't have to do it. I'll run your ads for you and follow
it. I'll run your ads for you and follow
it. I'll run your ads for you and follow up with those leads for you that would
up with those leads for you that would
up with those leads for you that would generate and I'll consult you and your
generate and I'll consult you and your
generate and I'll consult you and your team on how to actually convert the
team on how to actually convert the
team on how to actually convert the people we're bring to your
people we're bring to your
people we're bring to your door, right? Who do you think they're
door, right? Who do you think they're
door, right? Who do you think they're going to go with? Do you think they're
going to go with? Do you think they're
going to go with? Do you think they're going to keep paying that person that
going to keep paying that person that
going to keep paying that person that was providing a AI agent that answered
was providing a AI agent that answered
was providing a AI agent that answered calls? No, they're not. if I get my
calls? No, they're not. if I get my
calls? No, they're not. if I get my hands on them, it's a done deal, right?
hands on them, it's a done deal, right?
hands on them, it's a done deal, right? So, that's why I've been able to grow my
So, that's why I've been able to grow my
So, that's why I've been able to grow my business so quickly and make it be worth
business so quickly and make it be worth
business so quickly and make it be worth so much is because I have people that
so much is because I have people that
so much is because I have people that keep paying me and keep paying me that
keep paying me and keep paying me that
keep paying me and keep paying me that have been paying me for literally over 5
have been paying me for literally over 5
have been paying me for literally over 5 years for the same services. And I've
years for the same services. And I've
years for the same services. And I've added on new services as AI has come out
added on new services as AI has come out
added on new services as AI has come out and automations have improved. But it's
and automations have improved. But it's
and automations have improved. But it's not that to think you can just do it
not that to think you can just do it
not that to think you can just do it with a couple simple automations or a
with a couple simple automations or a
with a couple simple automations or a couple AI agents is pretty funny, right?
couple AI agents is pretty funny, right?
couple AI agents is pretty funny, right? And I think people that are promoting
And I think people that are promoting
And I think people that are promoting something like that don't actually know
something like that don't actually know
something like that don't actually know what it takes or know what it needs to
what it takes or know what it needs to
what it takes or know what it needs to be done to actually get local businesses
be done to actually get local businesses
be done to actually get local businesses to just justify paying you hundreds of
to just justify paying you hundreds of
to just justify paying you hundreds of thousands of dollars over the course of
thousands of dollars over the course of
thousands of dollars over the course of multiple years. But I do and this is
multiple years. But I do and this is
multiple years. But I do and this is exactly what it takes. So if this is
exactly what it takes. So if this is
exactly what it takes. So if this is something that you're serious about
something that you're serious about
something that you're serious about doing and something that you really want
doing and something that you really want
doing and something that you really want to do and take it to the next level, I'd
to do and take it to the next level, I'd
to do and take it to the next level, I'd love to talk with you about how I could
love to talk with you about how I could
love to talk with you about how I could help you to do that. Um because like I
help you to do that. Um because like I
help you to do that. Um because like I said, the reason why I'm doing this is
said, the reason why I'm doing this is
said, the reason why I'm doing this is because I'm looking to eventually sell
because I'm looking to eventually sell
because I'm looking to eventually sell my business down the line. And I spoke
my business down the line. And I spoke
my business down the line. And I spoke with a broker and he pretty much told
with a broker and he pretty much told
with a broker and he pretty much told me, "Look, if you can roll this thing up
me, "Look, if you can roll this thing up
me, "Look, if you can roll this thing up into a portfolio with multiple other
into a portfolio with multiple other
into a portfolio with multiple other agency owners, you could get instead of
agency owners, you could get instead of
agency owners, you could get instead of a 4x multiple an 8 to a 12, potentially
a 4x multiple an 8 to a 12, potentially
a 4x multiple an 8 to a 12, potentially even a 15x multiple, right? And by doing
even a 15x multiple, right? And by doing
even a 15x multiple, right? And by doing that, my business would go from being
that, my business would go from being
that, my business would go from being worth $5 million to 10 to 15, which is a
worth $5 million to 10 to 15, which is a
worth $5 million to 10 to 15, which is a massive difference for doing no
massive difference for doing no
massive difference for doing no additional work other than having
additional work other than having
additional work other than having someone else that does the same thing
someone else that does the same thing
someone else that does the same thing and has already done the work. So, uh,
and has already done the work. So, uh,
and has already done the work. So, uh, if that's something that you think you'd
if that's something that you think you'd
if that's something that you think you'd be interested in in talking about, I'd
be interested in in talking about, I'd
be interested in in talking about, I'd love to speak with you. Uh, if not, I
love to speak with you. Uh, if not, I
love to speak with you. Uh, if not, I hope you enjoyed this and I hope you got
hope you enjoyed this and I hope you got
hope you enjoyed this and I hope you got value from it. Look forward to seeing
value from it. Look forward to seeing
value from it. Look forward to seeing you soon.